http://www.bras-galore.com/pages/privacy-notice

bras-galore.com Ltd Privacy Notice
This privacy notice sets out how bras-galore.com Ltd (a UK registered company number 8179912) processes data. Where this is personal data, this document also highlights your rights in respect of that data. This notice was last updated on 24th May 2018. We regularly review and may occasionally amend this notice to reflect any new regulatory requirements and changes in our information collection and use. You should therefore return here regularly to view our most up to date privacy notice.
The types of data we process You may provide us with the following types of data when you interact with us directly, for example when browsing the website, placing an order, making an enquiry, opening or maintaining an account, or by signing up to receive our newsletter:
Identity - first name, last name, login information
Contact - email address, telephone numbers and postal address
Orders - purchased product and order data
Financial - payment details, billing address, payment history
Preferences - your marketing preferences
We may collect the following types of data when you browse our website (using Cookies or other tracking technologies):
Usage - data about how you use our website, including time spent on page, click-throughs, download errors
Technical - IP address, browser type, hardware type, network and software identifiers, device information, operating system and system configuration
How we process data
The table below sets out how we use data and our lawful basis for doing so. We may process your personal data for more than one lawful basis depending on the specific purpose for which we are using it. Importantly, we will only use your personal data when the law allows us to.
Our processing of data
Our lawful basis for doing this
Enable you to log in to and manage your account on our website
To enable the processing of payments which you make through our payment provider’s website
To arrange for the delivery of your order
Answer your enquiries which may involve contacting you by post, e-mail or phone
For performance of a contract with you.
To detect and prevent fraud.
To give you the opportunity to provide us with feedback through reviews and surveys
To Improve and personalise your experience of our website by delivering more relevant content.
The legitimate interests of bras-galore.com to develop our business, improve our website and overall user experience and inform our marketing strategy.
When you have purchased a product, or products, to highlight products that we think may be of interest to you, from time to time. You can opt-out from this at purchase time, or at any time thereafter.
The legitimate interests of bras-galore.com in maintaining a clear and open channel of communication with our valued customers and to maintain an ongoing relationship.
The right of individuals to unsubscribe from mailings and/or manage preferences will be noted within all mailings and any requests to unsubscribe may be made via links available in the mailings.
To keep you up to date on the products and services that we offer, through our occasional newsletter.
Your consent
To ensure the security of our systems, staff and premises (including the use of CCTV equipment)
The legitimate interests of bras-galore.com in protecting its systems, staff and premises from being misused or becoming subject to any criminal activity.
For internal administration and record keeping purposes
This is necessary for us to comply with our legal obligations.
The legitimate interests of bras-galore.com in administering, maintaining and continuously improving its systems and business processes.
To notify you of changes to our Privacy Notice, our Terms and Conditions or other changes to our services or products
This is necessary for us to comply with our legal obligations.
To anonymise and aggregate your personal data into an anonymised form that means that you cannot be personally identified
The legitimate interests of bras-galore.com in developing and testing its systems, carrying out research and general customer data analysis. Because this is not personally identifiable, we can use this for any purposes.
Transfers of Personal Data outside of the European Union
We use Shopify as our eCommerce platform and as such your personal data will be processed by Shopify in order to fulfil your order and to provide your account.
Shopify is Shopify Inc., a Canadian corporation with offices at 150 Elgin Street, Suite 800, Ottawa, ON, K2P 1L4, and its Irish affiliate Shopify International Ltd. (“Shopify”).
As part of our agreement with Shopify, they process your personal data in Ireland if you are located within the EEA and may transfer your personal data to other regions, including to Canada and the United States. Such transfers will always be completed in compliance with relevant Data Protection Legislation. IThe details of our arrangement with Shopify are available at https://www.shopify.com/legal/dpa should you wish to review them.
Rights of data subjects Data subjects in the European Union (or any jurisdiction with equivalent legislation to the European Union General Data Protection Regulation) have certain rights in respect of their personal data.
Any such data subject wishing to exercise any rights under applicable data protection laws (including the right to withdraw any consent to processing previously given; the right of access to data; or to have data corrected, updated, rectified or erased; or for access to data to be restricted or provided to any third party; or to object to any particular processing) should send the request to mail@bras-galore.com.
In any case in which a data subject chooses not to provide any personal data or where any of the rights set out above are exercised to limit the processing of personal data then bras-galore.com may be unable to provide relevant services, or there may be a restriction on the services which can be provided.
Corrections
We want to make sure that all of the information we hold about you is accurate and up to date so please let us know if we have got anything wrong, or if we can assist you to keep your data up-to-date. You can email your enquiry to mail@bras-galore.com
Retention
Bras-galore.com keeps data only for as long as it is necessary to fulfil the purposes for which we collected it. Our retention policy is to retain data in relation to a customer’s order for 6 years after the completion of that order. Any requests for for further information on retention should be sent to mail@bras-galore.com .
Contact Details
All enquiries relating to this notice should be sent to mail@bras-galore.com : Postal enquiries can be sent to The Data Protection Officer, bras-galore.com Ltd, 31 Harrington Road, Loddington, Northamptonshire, United Kingdom, NN14 1JZ.
Changes to this Privacy Notice
This privacy notice was last reviewed and updated on 24th May 2018. We keep this privacy notice under regular review and may occasionally amend it to reflect any new regulatory requirements and changes in our information collection and use. You should therefore return to www.bras-galore.com regularly to view our most up to date privacy notice.
